Local 1199 National Benefit and Pension Fund Records 6016
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Local 1199 National Benefit and Pension Fund Records
1973-1993
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees (NUHHCE)
NUHHCE Local 1199
6016
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Reports.
5758053
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, February 21, 2009
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 17, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5525: Local 1199 Additional Files 5680 OH: Local 1199 Oral History Project 5854: Local 1199 Additional Records 6016: Local 1199 National Benefit and Pension Fund Records 6062: Paul Friedman Collection of National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, Local 1199 Miscellany 6069: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Additional Files 6140: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project 6140 AV: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Audio Recordings
Hospitals--Staff--Labor unions; National Union of Hospital and Nursing Home Employees.; National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees --Archives; National Union of Hospital and Nursing Home Employees. Local 1199 Drug & Hospital Union (New York, N.Y.) --Archives
5758053
- Local 1199 Benefit Fund. Prescription Program / Dental Program., 1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Emerging Management Realities, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Author: Priscilla Elsass; Eileen Kaplan
    Notes: Prroceedings of the 35th Anniversary Meeting
    Format: Publication
    Language: English.
  - Item 2: Emerging Management Realities, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: Proceedings of the 35th Anniversary Meeting
- Dental Plan Manual., 1983; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Directory of Cooperating Dentists., 1988; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Directory of Cooperating Doctors., 1988; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Dental Plan Manual of Services for Cooperating Dentists., 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Directory of Cooperating Dentists., 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Directory of Cooperating Doctors., 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  April 1989.
- Directory of Cooperating Doctors., 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  May 1989. 2 Copies.
- Dental Plan Manual of Services for Cooperating Dentists., 1990; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Directory of Cooperating Dentists., 1990; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  March 1990.
- Directory of Cooperating Dentists., 1990; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  July 1990.
- Directory of Cooperating Doctors., 1990; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Medical Panel Handbook., 1990; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Directory of Cooperating Dentists., 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  March 1991.
- Directory of Cooperating Dentists., 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  November 1991. 2 copies.
- Directory of Cooperating Providers. Westchester Area., 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Preferred Provider Network. Methodist Hospital., 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Directory of Cooperating Dentists., 1992; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Directory of Cooperating Doctors., 1992; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
  2 copies.
- Preferred Provider Network. Hempstead General Hospital., 1992; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Directory of Cooperating Doctors., 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
- 1199 Panel Provider Bulletin., 1988; Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
  v.1:no.1 (1988:Fall)
- Bulletin., 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  no.1 (1988:Apr./May) and no.4 (1988/1989:Dec./Jan.). 2 copies each.
- 1199 Benefit Fund Program, Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Report on Your Funds., Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
- New Benefit Fund Program Combines Personal Attention and Low Cost, Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)